When 100% isn't enough.
200% Wolf is a animation, adventure, fantasy film directed by Alexs Stadermann.
When Freddy Lupin's wayward wish transforms him into a werewolf and deposits a mischievous moon
sprite on Earth, Freddy must restore the cosmic order before the earth and moon collide.
Batty (voice), played by Samara Weaving.
Max (voice), played by Jennifer Saunders.
Freddy Lupin (voice), played by Ilai Swindells.
Hamish (voice), played by Akmal Saleh.
Hotspur / Flasheart (voice), played by Peter McCallum.
Twitchy (voice), played by Sarah Rose Harper.
200% Wolf is a 2024 animated fantasy teen comedy film directed by Alexs
Stadermann and based on The Werewolf Saga by Jayne Lyons.
It serves as a sequel to the 2020 film 100% Wolf, focusing on Freddy's journey to
reclaim his inner wolf while facing new threats and challenges.
The film features voice performances from Samara Weaving, Jennifer Saunders, Ilai
Swindells, Akmal Saleh, Peter McAllum, Sarah Harper, and Elizabeth Nabben.
The film explores themes of werewolf, based on children's book, dog.
The tone is lighthearted.